Finding Aid for College of Pharmacy (University of Michigan) records, 1864-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Chronological Files 1868-1989
  - 1940-1989
    - 1976-1977
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 5)
      - Faculty-Staff Newsletter (Box 5)
      - Fund-Raising (Box 5)
      - Graduate Affairs & Research Committee (Box 5)
      - Peer College Visitations (Box 5)
      - Pre-Pharmacy (Box 5)
      - Searle Chair of Pharmacy (Box 5)
    - 1977-1978
      - Budget (Box 6)
      - Community Practice Grant (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 6)
      - Curriculum (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 6)
      - Faculty (Box 6)
      - Minority Students Project Grant (Box 6)
      - Ph.D. Review Committee (Box 6)
      - Promotion Policies, College of Pharmacy (Box 6)
    - 1978-1979
      - Budget (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 6)
      - Enrollment Statistics (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 6)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 6)
      - Minority Recruitment-Retention Program (Box 6)
      - Programs (Box 6)
    - 1979-1980
      - Accreditation Report (Box 6)
      - Budget (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 6)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 6)
      - Curriculum (Box 6)
      - Enrollment Statistics (Box 6)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 6)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 6)
      - N.I.H. Grant Requests (Box 6)
    - 1980-1981
      - Budget (Box 7)
      - College Status Report (Box 7)
      - Correspondence. External (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, Internal (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 7)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 7)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 7)
      - Graduate Affairs & Research Committee (Box 7)
      - Minority Recruitment-Retention Program (Box 7)
      - Minority Summer Program (Box 7)
      - Programs (Box 7)
    - 1981-1982
      - Accreditation Report (Box 7)
      - Budget (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 7)
      - Enrollment Statistics (Box 7)
      - Evaluation (A.C.P.E.) and Administrative Summary (Box 7)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 7)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 7)
      - Health Careers Grant (Box 7)
      - Minority Recruitment (Box 7)
      - Research Projects (Box 7)
      - Self Study Committee (Box 7)
    - 1982-1983
      - Budget (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, Internal (Box 7)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 7)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 7)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 7)
      - Gerontology (Box 7)
      - Programs (Box 7)
    - 1983-1984
      - Budget (Box 8)
      - Community-Based Program (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, External (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, Internal (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 8)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 8)
      - Faculty Minutes (Box 8)
      - Health Careers Grant (Box 8)
    - 1984-1985
      - Correspondence, External (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, Internal (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 8)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 8)
      - Programs (Box 8)
    - 1985-1986
      - Correspondence, External (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, Internal (Box 8)
      - Correspondence, University (Box 8)
      - Executive Committee Minutes (Box 8)
    - 1988-1989
      - A.C.P.E. Evaluation (Box 8)
- Photographs and Videotapes 1867-1973, 1993
  The Photographs / Visual Material Files contain 75 black and white positive images. They include class photographs, approximately 1867-1912, as well as photographs of alumni, conferences, facilities, faculty members, field trips, and honorary degree recipients. Also included is a recruiting videotape from 1993.
  - Alumni (Box 9)
  - Conferences (Box 9)
  - Facilities (Box 9)
  - Faculty Members (Box 9)
  - Field Trips (Box 9)
  - Honorary Degree Recipients (Box 9)
  - Recruiting Video: "Pharmacy: It's ore Than You Think," 1993, VHS tape (Box 9)
  - Class photographs 1867-1912, 2 folders (Box 11)
    (scattered dates)
  - Prescott Club Scrapbook (Box 11)
- Topical Files 1953-1992
  The Topical Files series is organized into four separate subseries covering different but partially overlapping time periods: 1953-1989, 1973-1992, 1953-1998 and 1971-1999. The 1953-1989 files are primarily from the deanship of Thomas Rowe while the 1973-1992 are primarily the period when Ara Paul served as Dean.
  - 1953-1989
    This Topical Files 1953-1989 subseries (1.5 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically. Among the significant files are American Council on Pharmaceutical Education, Clinical Appointments and Commencement.
    The American Council on Pharmaceutical Education files (.5 linear feet, 1972-1983) provides information about the operations and goals of the College of Pharmacy. There are several self studies and other reports relating to accreditation visits. The Annual Pharmacy Lectures (.1 linear foot, 1953-1982) subseries contains program pamphlets for the earlier years and some correspondence for the later years.
    The Clinical Appointments files (.25 linear feet, 1979-1988) contains information relating to the hiring of instructors. This part of the record group is restricted for 30 years from the date of creation of the records.
    The Commencement subseries (.25 linear feet, 1978-1986) contains files relating to graduation ceremonies and other events connected with those ceremonies. Interesting information about hall arrangements and physical room setup can be found in the ceremony arrangements folder. The majority of the information relates to the College of Pharmacy's own graduation ceremony, which changed names over the years from Senior Night to Senior Convocation to Pharmacy Convocation.
    - American Council on Pharmaceutical Education (ACPE) (Box 11)
    - Accreditation Standards and Guidelines 1984 (Box 9)
    - Annual Progress Reports 1973/74-1979/80, 7 folders (Box 9)
    - College of Pharmacy Self Study
      - 1972 (Box 9)
      - 1982 (Box 9)
      - Questionnaire 1982 (Box 9)
    - Accreditation Visits and Reports
      - 1976, 3 folders (Box 9)
      - 1977 (Box 9)
      - 1979-1983, 5 folders (Box 9)
    - Annual Pharmacy Lectures
      - 1953-1955, 1957-1961, 1963-1966, 1968-1973 (Box 10)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - 1977-1982, 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Budget (Box 10)
    - General Funds Requests
      - 1967-1969 (Box 10)
      - 1970/71-1975/76, 6 folders (Box 10)
      - 1972-1977 (Box 10)
      - 1973-1978 (Box 10)
    - Incremental Program Budget Requests 1971/72-1973/74, 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Clinical Appointments 1979-1988, 9 folders (Box 10)
    - Commencement
      - Expenses 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 10)
      - 1979 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1980 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1981 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1982 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1983 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1984 (Senior Night) (Box 10)
      - 1985 (Senior Convocation) (Box 10)
      - 1986 (Pharmacy Convocation) (Box 10)
    - Ceremony Arrangements 1980-1986 (Box 10)
    - Dean's Dinner 1981-1986 (Box 10)
    - Distinguished Alumni Award 1986 (Box 10)
    - Enrollment Statistics 1968-1970 (Box 10)
    - Self Study Conducted by Faculty, Students and Committees,1967-1970, Report on (Box 10)
    - Space Allocation and Utilization Committee Space Survey 1975-1979, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - 1973-1992
    The Topical Files, 1973-1992, subseries includes correspondence, reports, budget materials, curriculum materials, minutes and grant project descriptions. Primarily administrative in nature, the College of Pharmacy topical files contain several subjects of note.
    The Clerkship file (.25 linear feet, 1979-1991) documents graduate student field work, primarily through seminar overviews, syllabi, and administrative and curricular reports. The primary areas of field work documented in this file are clinical pharmacy, inpatient care, and ambulatory experience.
    Broader documentation of the College of Pharmacy's educational initiatives can be found in the Continuing Education file (.5 linear feet, 1981-1992). Materials include lecture series and conference descriptions, distance-education proposals, and certification and curriculum planning documents. Specific programs documented in this file include "Treatment of Infections in AIDS Patients," "The Practice of Clinical Nutrition," "Sports, Fitness and Pharmacy," "GI Disorders," "Communication Skill for Pharmacists," and "Computer Assisted Instruction."
    The Medicinal Chemistry specialization in the College of Pharmacy is documented through proposals for and descriptions of seminars, courses, and lecture series in the Medicinal Chemistry file (.15 linear feet, 1977-1992). Of particular interest are the programs and individual announcements for the Interdepartmental Graduate Seminar Program in Medicinal Chemistry. These materials document the medical professions' move towards interdisciplinary cooperation.
    Documentation of efforts to address minority recruitment is found in files on the Minority High School Student Research Apprentice Program (.1 linear feet, 1981-1988), as well as Minority Recruitment. The Minority High School Student Research Apprentice Program materials document the College of Pharmacy's program to introduce minority students to scientific research. Of particular interest are the student descriptions of the work they performed and their evaluations of the program.
    The Minority Recruitment materials consists of reports by Valener Perry, the head recruiting officer, application and enrollment statistics, and materials from recruitment program. Perry's reports provide an overview of recruitment activities and recruitment sites pursued by the College. One well documented outreach program is the 1991 Washtenaw Community College-University of Michigan Alliance for Minority Scholars. Other materials of interest include participant evaluations of recruitment programs.
    The College of Pharmacy's relationship with the University Hospitals is documented in the Pharmacy Services file (.2 linear feet, 1986-1992). Materials include descriptions of prospective courses aimed at introducing Pharmacy students to hospital services, and programs for interdepartmental activities. Of particular importance are records documenting the cost increase in pharmaceuticals and pharmacy education due primarily to genetic engineering.
    The Planning Project file (.1 linear feet, 1973-1978) contains reports and discussions of objectives of individual academic units within the College, information on fields of practice and programs of study in the College's history, and statistical and analytical budget data. Issues raised in the reports include faculty overload/budget restraints, baccalaureate and Pharm.D. (Ph.D. equivalent) curricula, pharmaceutical practice settings in Michigan, student counseling, and multidisciplinary research.
    - Biomedical Research Support Group 1982-1989, 5 folders (Box 12)
    - Budget 1986-1989, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Career Guidance and Placement Service 1982-1983 (Box 12)
    - Centennial Symposium 1976 (Box 12)
    - Clerkships 1979-1991, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Commencement 1987-1990, 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Committee for Gender Research 1982 (Box 12)
    - Committee Rosters 1983-1988 (Box 12)
    - Computer Use and Resources 1982-1986, 4 folders (Box 12)
    - Continuing Education
      - 1981-1983 (Box 12)
      - 1985-1986 (Box 12)
      - 1987 (Box 13)
      - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
      - 1990 (Box 13)
      - 1991 (Box 13)
      - 1992 (Box 13)
    - Course Information 1978-1993, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Credit Evaluation and Advanced Standing Committee 1980 (Box 13)
    - Curriculum Committee 1981-1986, 6 folders (Box 13)
    - Departmental Administration 1984-1989 (Box 13)
    - Enrollment Statistics 1981-1983, 1988, 1991 (Box 13)
    - Equipment Needs 1976-1985, 1989, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Faculty Handbook
      - 1981 (Box 13)
      - 1983 (Box 13)
      - 1984 (Box 13)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1981-1990, 2 folders (Box 13)
    - Fellowship Opportunities 1982-1991 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Affairs Committee 1981-1985 (Box 13)
    - Honor Council Constitution 1986 (Box 13)
    - Manpower 1976-1978 (Box 13)
    - Medicinal Chemistry (Box 14)
    - Blicke Seminar 1980-1983 (Box 14)
    - General Files 1977-1988, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Medicinal Chemistry Meeting Minutes 1976-1991 (Box 17)
      - Meeting Minutes 1976-1982 (Box 17)
        [RESTRICTED until July 1, 2057 ]
      - Meeting Minutes 1983-1991 (Box 17)
    - Seminars 1979-1992, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Minority High School Student Research Apprentice Program 1981-1988, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Minority Recruitment 1972-1991, 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Minority Recruitment. NIH Grant 1972-1979 (Box 14)
    - Pharmaceutics Seminar 1978-1993 (Box 14)
      (scattered)
    - Pharmacy Advancement Program 1983-1992 (Box 14)
    - Pharmacy Research Building 1987 (Box 14)
    - Pharmacy Services 1986-1992, 6 folders (Box 14)
    - Pharm.D. (Ph.D. equivalent) 1986-1992, 2 folders (Box 14)
    - Planning Project 1973-1978, 1984 (Box 15)
    - Practice Faculty Meeting Minutes 1980-1982 (Box 15)
    - President's Office 1991 (Box 15)
    - Press Releases 1973-1981 (Box 15)
    - Promotion Considerations 1982 (Box 17)
      [RESTRICTED until July 1, 2017 ]
    - Recommendations 1983-1989 (Box 17)
      [RESTRICTED until July 1, 2019 ]
    - Report on Pharmacy Education
      - 1972 (Box 15)
      - 1976 (Box 15)
      - 1982 (Box 15)
      - 1984 (Box 15)
    - Research Incentive Accounts 1983-1992 (Box 15)
    - Research, Vice President for 1990-1992 (Box 15)
    - Salary Surveys 1976-1987, 6 folders (Box 15)
    - Salary and Appointment Statistics 1982-1986, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Scholarships (Box 15)
    - General 1987-1991 (Box 15)
    - Academic Recognition Scholarship 1987-1990, 2 folders (Box 17)
      - Academic Recognition Scholarship 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 17)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2063 ]
      - Academic Recognition Scholarship 1989-1990, 2 folders (Box 17)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2065 ]
    - Senior Class Night 1974-1976, 1978 (Box 15)
    - Small Instrumentation Grant 1987-1989 (Box 15)
    - Students (Undergraduates) 1988-1992 (Box 15)
    - Summer Undergraduate Research Program 1987-1990 (Box 15)
    - Upjohn Center for Clinical Pharmacology 1977-1983, 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Upjohn Conference for the Improvement of College and University Science Teaching 1986 (Box 15)
    - Upjohn Pharmacy Research Award 1987-1993 (Box 15)
    - Utilization Analysis 1986 (Box 15)
    - Veterans Administration 1973-1981 (Box 15)
  - 1951-1998
    Topical Files, 1951-1998 subseries (bulk 1977-1998, 5.5 linear ft) acessioned in 2000, are primarily from the tenure of Dean Ara Paul. The subseries includes Dean Paul's daily correspondence file which spans from 1987 to 1994, commencement files for the period of 1991-1997, and Faculty Meeting minutes for the same time period. The series also supplements the 1996 accession with documentation on the Continuing Education Program, Medicinal Chemistry program, Minority Recruitment, as well as the relationship with the University Hospitals.
    - Ad Hoc Committee 1985-1992 (Box 18)
    - Affirmative Action Committee 1978-1988 (Box 18)
    - Ambulatory Care Fellowship 1988-1990 (Box 18)
    - American Caner Society Grant 1963-1967 (Box 18)
    - American Council on Pharmaceutical Education Evaluation 1988 (Box 18)
    - Biomedical Research Support 1991-1993, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Biomedical Research Support Grant 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - Budget Conference 1977 (Box 18)
    - Budget Data 1987-1994, 7 folders (Box 18)
    - Centennial Celebration 1976 (Box 18)
    - Clinical Pharmacy Group 1975 (Box 18)
    - Clinical Research Center 1989-1994 (Box 18)
    - Clinical Research Fellowship 1989 (Box 18)
    - Commencement 1991-1997, 7 folders (Box 18)
    - Committee Directories 1979-1982 (Box 18)
    - Continuing Education, proposed plan 1988 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence with James Duderstadt 1986-1987 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, daily 1987, 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, daily 1988-1992, 14 folders (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, daily 1992-1994, 8 folders (Box 20)
    - Correspondence with Professor Richard Deno 1951-1967 (Box 20)
    - Curriculum Committee 1987-1992, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Curriculum and Program Background Files 1976-1979 (Box 20)
    - Curriculum Faculty Retreat June 24, 1992 (Box 20)
    - Curriculum, Pharm D Program 1986 (Box 20)
    - Department of Pharmacy Services, Cost Effectiveness Program Plan 1992 (Box 20)
    - Distinguished Faculty Achievement Award 1987-1994 (Box 20)
    - Evaluation and Planning Project 1977 (Box 20)
    - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1991-1996, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - Faculty Retreat April 11, 1987 (Box 21)
    - King/Chavez/Parks Visiting Professor Program 1988-1992 (Box 21)
    - Medical Chemistry Group 1973-1976 (Box 21)
    - Medical Chemistry Program, General 1989-1990 (Box 21)
    - Medical School 1988-1995 (Box 21)
    - Medicinal Chemistry Program, Committee and Faculty Minutes 1992-1996 (Box 21)
    - Michigan Association of Governing Boards, Faculty Awards 1988-1995 (Box 21)
    - Minority Affairs 1991-1994 (Box 21)
    - Minority Enrollment 1991-1994 (Box 21)
    - Minority High School Student Research Apprentice Program 1992-1995, 3 folders (Box 21)
    - National Institute of Health Construction Grant 1993 (Box 21)
    - Pharmaceutics, General 1989-1991 (Box 21)
    - Pharmaceutics Program 1975-1977 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacognosy 1987-1990 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Administration Program 1987-1992 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Advancement Program 1994-1995 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy D Investigations Committee 1975-1988 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy D Program 1977-1993 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Search Committee 1972-1985 (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Services, Department of 1977-1983, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Pharmacy Services, Department of 1984-1985 (Box 22)
    - Prescott Circle Dinner October 20, 1995 (Box 22)
    - Rosa Parks Visiting Professor Program 1987 (Box 22)
    - Report on Program Cost Construction 1977 (Box 22)
    - Rho Chi Society 1972-1995 (Box 22)
    - Saxon Pharmacy Project 1991 (Box 22)
    - Small Instrumentation Program 1989-1995, 6 folders (Box 22)
    - Space Allocation and Utilization Committee 1980-1987 (Box 22)
    - Steering Committee Meeting Materials 1992 (Box 22)
    - Strategic Planning Retreat 1987 (Box 22)
    - Student Awards 1988-1995 (Box 22)
    - Student Class Lists and Directories 1989-1998 (Box 22)
    - Student Groups Leaders List 1988-1995 (Box 22)
    - Student Papers, Pharmacy 420 1990 (Box 22)
    - Subcommittee on Effective Teaching 1985-1993 (Box 22)
    - Summer Research Apprentice Program for High School Students 1989-1992, 3 folders (Box 22)
    - Unit for Laboratory Animal Medicine 1988-1996 (Box 23)
    - University Hospital Pharmacy 1977-1983 (Box 23)
    - University Hospitals, General 1978-1986 (Box 23)
    - University Hospitals, Pharmacy Operations Review 1986 (Box 23)
    - University Seminar 1993 (Box 23)
    - Upjohn Center Policy Committee 1979 (Box 23)
    - Volwiler Award 1993 (Box 23)
  - 1971-1999 (scattered)
    The Topical Files, 1971-1999 subseries (accessioned in 2004) is arranged alphabetically, except for daily correspondence, which is located in a separate box (files within daily correspondence are arranged chronologically). Notable files in the Topical Files series include ACPE evaluations and reports, College of Pharmacy histories, Strategic Planning Committee files, and the dean's daily correspondence files.
    - ACPE Accreditation Action and Recommendations June 1997 (Box 25)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2034 ]
    - ACPE Administrative Summary February 1997 (Box 25)
    - ACPE Self Study Report February 1997 (Box 25)
    - Administrative Summary and Questionnaire for the ACPE Evaluation Visit March 1997 (Box 25)
    - Dean Search and Background Materials 1967-1976 1971-1975, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - The Evaluation Team Report of the Professional Program Leading to the Doctor of Pharmacy Degree (ACPE) March 1997 (Box 25)
    - Box 25 (cont.) Guidelines to Minimize Exposure to HIV, HBV, and Other Bloodborne Pathogens February 1993 (Box 25)
    - Histories circa 1971, circa 1976, circa 1995 (Box 25)
    - Self Study Report of the University of Michigan College of Pharmacy Graduate Program January 1995, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Strategic Planning Committee
      - June 28, 1996 (Box 25)
      - July 12, 1996 (Box 25)
      - August 9, 1996 (Box 25)
      - August 23, 1996 (Box 25)
      - September 13, 1996 (Box 25)
      - September 27, 1996 (Box 25)
      - October 25, 1996 (Box 25)
      - December 13, 1996 (Box 25)
      - March 14, 1997 (Box 25)
      - April 11, 1997, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - May 1, 1997 (Box 25)
      - June 27, 1997 (Box 25)
      - September 12, 1997 (Box 25)
      - October 10, 1997 (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, daily July 1994-May 1999, 59 folders (Box 26)
  - 1917-2003
    (2008-2011 accession)
    - A.B. Prescott Student Chapter, American Pharmaceutical Association, Meeting Minutes 1946-1954 (Box 29)
    - Alumni Society
      - Constitution and By-Laws undated (Box 29)
      - Induction 1994 (Box 29)
    - Alumni Survey undated (Box 29)
    - Annual Giving 1978-1986 (Box 29)
    - Board of Governors
      - General 1979-1999 (21 folders, photos in 1992 folder) (Box 29)
      - Nominations
        - 1995 (Box 29)
        - 1996 (Box 29)
      - Strategic Planning Retreat
        - 1997 (Box 29)
        - Photo Album 1999 (Box 11)
      - Subcommittee on Curriculum Revision 1992-1993 (Box 29)
    - Career Planning and Placement Center 1976 (Box 29)
    - Class of 1951 Newsletter, undated (Box 29)
    - Class of 1960 Composite (outsize) (Box 29)
    - Class Reunions
      - 1979 Class Officers (Box 29)
      - 1989
        - General (Box 29)
        - Secretaries (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘44 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘49 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘54 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘59 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘64 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘69 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘74 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘79 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘84 (Box 29)
      - 1990
        - General (Box 29)
        - Agents (Box 29)
        - Secretaries (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘45 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘50 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘55 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘60 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘65 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘70 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘75 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘80 (Box 29)
        - Class of ‘85 (Box 29)
      - 1991
        - Class of ’46-Secretary Tharon DeYoung (Box 29)
        - Class of ’51-Secretary Paul Smith (Box 29)
        - Class of ’56-Secretaries Roger and Anne Curran (Box 29)
        - Class of ’61-Secretaries Jerome and Mildred (Midge) Mills (Box 29)
        - Class of ’66-Secretaries Peter and Arlene Reilly, Richard Hutchinson (Box 29)
        - Class of ’71-Secretary Greg Raiss (Box 29)
        - Class of ’76-Secretary James Lang (Box 29)
        - Class of ’81-Secretary Nancy Bicknell (Box 29)
        - Class of ’86-Secretary Julie Botsford (Box 29)
        - Mattocks Reunion (Box 29)
    - College Awards (Box 30)
      - 125th Anniversary Plaque 2001 (Box 30)
      - American Pharmaceutical Association Academy of Students of Pharmacy Certificate of Recognition for Participation in Chapter Achievement Award Competition 1991 (Box 30)
    - College Report 1987 (Box 30)
    - Commencement 1999 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence
      - General 1976-1979 (Box 30)
      - Dean George Kenyon 1999-2003, 3 folders (Box 30)